https://ironsidestech.com/privacy-policy/

Ironsides Technology Privacy Policy
When you communicate with us, you trust us with your information. We provide this Privacy Policy to help you understand what data we collect, why we collect it, and what we do with it.
This website is owned by Ironsides Technology, LLC. (“Ironsides”, “we” or “us”) whose registered office address is 238 Littleton Road, Westford, MA 01886, USA. We are the ‘data controller’ of the personal information you provide to us. This Privacy Policy governs your interactions with Ironsides Technology and its subsidiaries.
Through the course of our business activity, including interactions with you, we may receive information that identifies you. For example, you might send us an email; you might complete a form on our website; you might call to speak with one of our representatives, or we may meet with you or another person with whom you work.
We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This privacy policy statement summarizes what personal information we may collect from you and what we will do with it.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT
We collect and securely store a limited set of personal information for our legitimate business purpose to provide services to our existing and potential customers. This personal information includes your name, titles, telephone numbers, physical addresses and email addresses. In addition, we record other information arising from the commercial activity between us.
Some information (like your name and email address) may be recorded in a documentary record (for example, in sales quotations and support logs or in notes of interactions we have had). If you share another person’s data with us (for example, if you purchase a software license for another member of your organization), you will need to check that such person consents to your providing that information to us.
WHEN DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION?
We collect information from you when you fill out a form or enter information on our website.
HOW WE USE THE DATA
Our purpose for having this personal information is so that we (including our subsidiaries) can provide you with information relevant to the products or services we offer. As our commercial activity is fundamentally business to business, our use of such information is to fulfill the legitimate interest we have in serving our business clients. We use personal information only in a way that a person would reasonably expect a business such as ours to do. At your request, we will work with a third party to provide you with information. For example, the company for which you work may want us to work with a third party to service a solution that involves a product we produce.
In addition to the above, we may use the information held about you to:
Notify you of any changes to our products.
Ensure that the content of our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and your computer.
Provide you with information, products and services requested from us.
Provide you with helpful information about our products or services which you use, including any software updates for our products.
Allow you to participate in interactive features of our offering, should you choose to do so.
Perform our obligations concerning any contracts entered into between you and us, including under relevant product warranties.
When required, we will get your permission to share your information with a third party prior to providing it to the third party; however, we will accept direction to share information from someone we believe has reasonable authority to direct such communication (for example, your work supervisor).
At any time, you can opt out from receiving communication from us by sending your request to info@IronsidesTech.com or by mail at our registered office address. We will act in a timely manner to update our records appropriately and to comply with your request and relevant regulations.
HOW DO WE STORE AND PROTECT YOUR DATA?
We will securely and privately keep and manage personal information in accordance with prevailing law. We will not sell or rent your personal information, and we will not disclose personal information to third parties (other than as listed below) unless we are required to do so by law.
THIRD PARTIES WHO PROVIDE SERVICES ON OUR BEHALF
We may share your personal information with certain third parties who provide services on our behalf. In such event, they will have access to only the personal information they need to perform those services. They are required to keep your personal information secure and confidential and may only use it as permitted by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
We may also share personal information among Ironsides Technology and its subsidiaries in accord with our legitimate business interests.
The third parties who provide services on our behalf fall into the following categories:
Our distributors and resellers and services agents
Technology providers performing services for us
Marketing agencies performing services for us
HOW LONG DO WE STORE YOUR DATA?
We will not keep your data for longer than is reasonably necessary for the relevant purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. As we typically sell product to a company rather than an individual, we will typically hold personal information associated with a company until we are notified a person no longer works for that company (or in a relevant capacity); however, as a policy, we may hold personal information until a period of 6 years passes without any contact with the relevant individual or until that individual requests we delete such information, whichever occurs first.
YOUR RIGHTS
Under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and The Data Protection Act 2018 (DPA) you have a number of rights with regard to your personal data. You have the right to request from us access to and rectification or erasure of your personal data, the right to restrict processing, the right to object to processing, as well as the right to data portability in certain circumstances.
If you have provided consent for the processing of your data, you have the right (in certain circumstances) to withdraw that consent at any time which will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before your consent was withdrawn. You have the right to lodge a complaint to your relevant Supervisory Authority if you believe that we have not complied with the requirements of the GDPR or DPA with regard to your personal data.
CHANGE OF CONTROL PROVISION
In the event of a sale, transfer, merger, change of control, consolidation, reorganization or liquidation of Ironsides Technology, we may sell, transfer or assign information you have provided to us to a third party, including such information as, but not limited to, personally identifiable information and other information concerning your relationship with us.
COOKIES
We may use “cookies” to help us recognize you on any return visits you make to our website and to make any registration or other procedures easier for you. Cookies are small pieces of information which are stored by your browser. If you do not want your browser to store such cookies, you should review your browser’s documentation and settings for privacy, security and cookies and take appropriate action; however, by restricting or disabling cookies you may be unable to access certain parts of our website or others that are important to you. For more information on cookies, please visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org
To change your allowance for the use of cookies you may click the Revoke button and then Reject from the cookie notice: Revoke cookies
THIRD PARTY WEBSITES
From time to time our website may contain links to and from third-party websites. Such third-party websites have their own privacy policies and you should check these before submitting any personal data. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for the policies or practices of such a third party.
CONTACTING US
If you would like us to remove your personal information from our marketing database, or if you would otherwise like to communicate with us, please write to us at our registered office address or by email to info@IronsidesTech.com.
CHANGES
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post changes to our Privacy Policy in a manner that will make them reasonably easy to find and to understand, as well as to accept or to decline should your approval of such changes be required under GDPR or other regulations. We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for you to be able to review.
IRONSIDES TECHNOLOGY LLC.
238 Littleton Road, Westford, MA 01886, USA
SIGN UP FOR OUR MAILING LIST
Receive our exclusive newsletter and content
Solutions
Resources
Partners
About Us
Careers
Contact Us
News & Events
Sitemap
IRONSIDES TECHNOLOGY LLC.
238 Littleton Road, Westford, MA 01886, USA
Solutions
Resources
Partners
About Us
Careers
Contact Us
News & Events
Sitemap
SIGN UP FOR OUR MAILING LIST
Receive our exclusive newsletter and content
IRONSIDES TECHNOLOGY LLC.
238 Littleton Road, Westford, MA 01886, USA
Solutions
Resources
Partners
About Us
Careers
Contact Us
News & Events
Sitemap
SIGN UP FOR OUR MAILING LIST
Receive our exclusive newsletter and content
Copyright © 2020 Ironsides Technology LLC. All rights reserved. | Privacy Policy
Let's Connect
Let’s Connect!
Name *FirstLastCompany Name *Company Email *Phone NumberComment or MessageMessageSubmit
X
Let's Connect
Name *FirstLastCompany Name *Company Email *Phone NumberComment or MessageEmailSubmit
X
See our updated response to Covid-19 HERE
X
Update on COVID-19
Ironsides Technology continues to monitor the rapidly evolving situation relating to the global spread of COVID-19.
We are following the advice and guidelines of the World Health Organisation and public health authorities in each country we operate in. Implementation of these guidelines is being coordinated by our health and safety teams and all of Ironsides fully supports this vital effort.
We are working hard to ensure we remain a safe, strong and well managed partner, one that can operate successfully during these difficult times and support our customer’s return to normal operations in the near future. Robust business continuity and precautionary measures are in place across our global operations network.
We are reviewing and modifying our response as the situation evolves. We express our sincere thanks to our entire staff across Ironsides Technology, who are doing a terrific job in a highly professional manner, in difficult and worrying circumstances.
These are challenging times. Please remember to follow official guidelines and stay safe.
Close
Let's Connect
Name *FirstLastTitle *Company Name *Company Email *Phone NumberComment or MessageNameSubmit
X
We use cookies within our website to provide the best viewing experience, to continue using cookies click Accept, otherwise click Reject. You may revoke cookie acceptance through the Privacy Policy page at any time.AcceptRejectPrivacy policy
You can revoke your consent any time using the Revoke consent button.Revoke cookies
